Privacy Policy
==============

_Last Updated Nov 23, 2020_

Thank you for your interest in Honeyfund.com, Inc. (referred to herein as "we" or "us") and our website, [Honeyfund.com](http://www.honeyfund.com/) (the "Site"). References to “you” or “your” contained in this privacy policy means, you, the individual user or visitor of the Site. This privacy policy was created to let you know why we collect information from you and what we do with it. By using the Site, you consent to the following terms. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use the Site.

This statement discloses the privacy practices of Honeyfund.com, Inc. It covers:

1. The Information We Collect From You on the Site
2. How We Use the Information We Collect From You
3. How We Share Your Information
4. Accessing, Changing or Deleting your Personal Information
5. California and European Union Data Rights
6. Miscellaneous Disclosures

#### 1\. The Information We Collect From You on the Site

Honeyfund.com, Inc. collects information from you depending upon your engagement with our Site as detailed more fully in this section. We collect personal information, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, postal address, zip code and other contact details (“Personal Information”). As noted in the following sections, we will also collect additional information based upon a particular interaction with our Site, including registration or in providing a gift to a registered couple or purchasing an eGiftCard. We also collect information about your use of the website including technical information, such as the date and time you access the Site, your internet protocol address, browser name, computing device type, and service usage information such as records and history about transactions and preferences you have made on our Site, and demographic, geographic and psychographic information (collectively, “Browsing Information”).

### Information collected at registration

Honeyfund.com, Inc. collects Personal Information when you register with us and when you use Honeyfund services. Honeyfund.com, Inc. will combine this information about you with information we obtain from third party business partners. Our third party business partners include (1) retailers that enable you to choose to use our services in connection with your wedding registry and/or shopping with such retailers; (2) social media networks that permit you to interface your social media account with our Site; and (3) third party advertising companies who sell advertisements on our Site, (4) payment providers who process your payments for gifts or gift cards purchased on our site. During registration, we require members to provide us with Personal Information, and additional information, such as your future spouse's first and last name, your wedding date, preferred honeymoon destination, and demographic information, including your ZIP or postal code. The information we collect regarding your spouse has the chance of revealing your sexual orientation. We do not record any member's sexual orientation, but due to the legally recognized nature of this information, we will collect your explicit consent to process this piece of information only as necessary to render our services through the site to you.

In addition to the questions you answer when you register for Honeyfund.com membership, we collect information necessary to create your honeymoon registry, including but not limited to at least one registry item the couple would like to receive as a gift and a contact person for the account.

Registration information provided to us through the Site is collected via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol (https). Although additional demographic information may be requested at the time of registration, only information marked "required" is necessary for registration and utilization of our services.

Users who register for our Site through Facebook will be prompted through Facebook's website or application permissions interface to agree to share their public Facebook profile, friend list and e-mail address with us. Facebook is a joint data controller and has collected the information from your public Facebook profile, friend list and email address to provide to us with your affirmative consent. Facebook is responsible for that data, which is provided to Honeyfund.com, Inc.

### Information collected from the Give a Gift process

Users who give gifts to Honeyfund.com members or purchase through shop.honeyfund.com are not required to register. However, some information is collected during the "Give a Gift" or Checkout process, including Personal Information, such as first and last name, e-mail address and/or phone number. This Personal Information may be linked with the member's account for whom the gift is being provided.

We do not accept registrations from persons under the age of 18. Honeyfund services are available only to persons who are 18 years of age and over. If we learn that a user is under the age of 18, we will terminate the account and delete the user's information. Honeyfund.com, Inc. will not be liable for any content or advertisements viewed by minor children in violation of the terms of this agreement.

### Information collected through use of Honeyfund.com

Honeyfund.com, Inc. collects Browsing Information whenever you visit the Site.

Honeyfund.com, Inc. and its third party business partners and advertising companies use internet cookies on the Site. Internet cookies are small data files that are sent by us to you and stored on your computer. The internet cookies provide us with Browsing Information.

This Site uses Google Analytics, which collects Browsing Information from you and provides us with information on our user traffic to the Site, Site usage, demographics and interests of Site visitors. This Browsing Information is collected by a Google Analytics cookie and reported to us.

You can browse the Honeyfund.com website without registering or providing any Personal Information, but we do collect Browsing Information as detailed in this policy. In order to take advantage of our honeymoon registry service, you are required to provide us with Personal Information.

#### 2\. How We Use the Information We Collect From you

The Personal and Browsing Information we collect from your membership helps us to create your online account and make your registry available to your guests, improve our content, customize certain pages for you, make third-party payment systems available to you, and with your affirmative consent, provide you with promotional information and updates about Honeyfund.com, Inc. and its affiliates.

The name and e-mail address collected during the “Give a Gift” or eGift Card purchase process is not shared with third parties, but it is used by Honeyfund.com, Inc. and Site members to communicate with the gift giver regarding their gift and to announce future features, product updates and offers.

We use your Browsing Information to identify the geographic locations where our visitors originate, to examine overall Site traffic trends, for system administration, troubleshooting, security and fraud prevention, and to improve and optimize your user experience on the website. We record this information in aggregate form and link to accounts and Personal Information to prevent spam e-mail activities using Honeyfund.com, Inc.'s email feature. We also use Browsing Information to customize portions of our Site to your preferences. For example, Honeyfund.com, Inc. uses a cookie to identify you as a Honeyfund.com member and to provide you with access to your personal account. This way, you don't have to login every time you come to the Honeyfund.com website. If you do not allow your browser to accept cookies, please understand that some of the areas or functionality within our site will be limited.

Unfortunately no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, you acknowledge that (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party.

#### 3\. How We Share Your Information

Honeyfund.com, Inc. shares Personal Information and Browsing Information we collect about you with third parties who perform services for us and with whom we contract in order to provide you with the functions and services available through our Site. These third parties include our payment card processors, email delivery providers, gift card redemption provider, and advertising providers who sell advertisements on our Site. Our payment card processors receive your name, payment card information, contact information, and any other information necessary to process your transaction. Our email delivery providers receive your email address and user ID. Our advertising business partners receive your Browsing Information, including internet protocol address, web history, and other demographic and internet usage information. We will also provide information necessary to our third party payment card processors to prevent fraud or other harm occurring through our Site.

In the event that Honeyfund.com, Inc., or substantially all of its assets are sold or Honeyfund.com, Inc. is reorganized or merged into another organization, your Personal Information and Browsing Information will be among Honeyfund.com, Inc. transferred assets.

There may be rare instances in which we are required to disclose your Personal Information, Browsing Information, or both as required by law and as necessary to comply with a judicial or administrative proceeding, court order or legal process services on us. We will also disclose information as required to protect our rights

#### 4\. Accessing, Changing or Deleting your Personal Information

You can access or update your Personal Information by logging in to your Honeyfund.com account and changing your profile. If you would like to deactivate your membership, use the following Web page address [https://www.honeyfund.com/CloseAccount](https://www.honeyfund.com/CloseAccount). You may also contact Honeyfund.com, Inc. by e-mailing [help@honeyfund.com](https://info.honeyfund.com/help/kb-tickets/new) and writing "Deactivate Membership" in the subject line or write to Honeyfund.com, Inc. at 2519 McMullen Booth Rd, Ste 510-260, Clearwater, FL 33761. This action will remove your registry page from public access. Note: It will not remove your registry page from any search engine cache. To remove your information from search engine cache, contact the search engine directly. To delete your information from Honeyfund databases, e-mail [help@honeyfund.com](https://info.honeyfund.com/help/kb-tickets/new) and writing “Delete Information” in the subject line or write to Honeyfund.com, Inc. at 2519 McMullen Booth Rd, Ste 510-260, Clearwater, FL 33761.

#### 5\. California and European Union Data Rights

### California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”)

Beginning on January 1, 2020, a California resident has the right to request a business that collects, shares, and sells personal information about the consumer to provide certain information in relation to those activities.

A California resident also has the right to opt-out of having their information sold to a third party. Specifically, a California consumer has the right, at any time, to direct a business that sells personal information about the consumer to third parties not to sell the consumer's personal information. Honeyfund.com, Inc. does not sell any of your Personal Information to any third parties.

### California Do Not Track Disclosures

Certain browsers include functionality which enables a user to indicate they do not wish to be tracked, with respect to the collection of their Personal Information over time and across third-party websites or online services. We do not honor “Do Not Track” signals from internet web browsers. For more information on how to opt-out of Google Analytics, please visit: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

### European Union Data Rights

The European Union's (“EU”) General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) requires that certain information be provided to data subjects when their personal data is collected, which is detailed below. References in this section to terms such as “controller,” “data subject,” “personal data,” “processor,” and “supervisory authority” shall have the meanings set forth in Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016.

* The controller of the personal data collected on this Site is Rachel Harris, Director of Customer Service, Honeyfund.com, Inc., 2519 McMullen Booth Rd, Ste 510-260, Clearwater, FL 33761, support@honeyfund.com. Honeyfund.com, Inc.'s GDPR representative can be contacted by e-mailing support@honeyfund.com.
* Personal data is processed for the purposes detailed in this privacy policy. The legal basis for the processing activities detailed in this privacy policy is by consent, where indicated, and pursuant to contract with us, pursuant to our Terms of Use.
* We provide personal data to third parties in accordance with this privacy policy, including third party service providers that render services to us by contract.
* The personal data we collect pursuant to this privacy policy is stored until you contact us to request deletion of the information.
* Where personal data is collected from you on the Site or through communications with us and is deemed as being required or mandatory for you to provide us, this data is necessary in order for us to provide you with the requested service or to enable you to engage in a particular function on our Site. If you choose against providing us with the required information, you will not be permitted to receive the particular service or engage in the desired function.
* Honeyfund.com, Inc. has Sites in the United States and the United Kingdom. To the extent any information must be transferred to a third country or international organization, Honeyfund.com, Inc. will comply with the applicable data privacy laws, including execution of the Standard Contractual Clauses as approved by the European Commission.

### European Union Data Rights

EU data subjects have certain data rights under the GDPR, including the right to request access to and rectification of their personal data. Further, a data subject has the right to request erasure of their personal data or for a restriction of processing as it concerns such data subject. The data subject has the right to object to processing and a right to data portability. A data subject has the right to lodge a complaint against us with a supervisory authority. To the extent the processing of your personal data is based upon your consent, you have the right to withdraw your consent and exercise your data rights at any time by contacting us at the address above.

#### 6\. Miscellaneous Disclosures

### Transactional Emailing

Honeyfund.com may send transactional emails based on website activity including but not limited to important account information, receipts, financial changes, and abandoned checkout reminders.

### Other websites

The Honeyfund.com website contains links to other websites. We cannot be responsible for their content or for private information that you may choose to share with them. Please note: Information you release directly to parties who provide services to Honeyfund.com, Inc., such as any vendors who advertise on the Honeyfund.com website, may be subject to different rules of use or disclosure. We encourage you to investigate and ask questions before disclosing personal information to third parties.

### Disclaimer

Your privacy is very important to us, but due to the existing legal regulatory and security environment, we cannot fully ensure that your private communications and other Personal Information will not be disclosed to third parties. Under certain circumstances, the government or third parties may lawfully or unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Additionally, in the unlikely event we need to investigate or resolve possible problems or inquiries, we may disclose information about you to private entities, law enforcement, or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.

### Notice of changes

Honeyfund.com, Inc. reserves the right to change this privacy policy in its sole discretion, and will post any revisions on this Site. In the event of a material change to this privacy policy, we will post a notice on our main Site drawing your attention to such changes. We encourage you to review this privacy policy regularly for any changes. Except as otherwise prohibited by applicable Law, your continued use of the Site will be subject to the then-current privacy policy and will constitute your acknowledgement of the modified policy and agreement to abide and be bound by the modified policy. If there is a change in this privacy policy that affects your Personal Information, we will notify you of the change by e-mail to the address that you have provided to us. At the time of this message, you will be given the option to opt out of this change in information usage by sending a message to [help@honeyfund.com](https://info.honeyfund.com/help/kb-tickets/new), provided, however that any subsequent use of the Site will subject you to the new privacy policy.

Honeyfund.com, Inc. encourages you to learn as much as you can about your privacy on the Internet. To find out more, visit [www.bbbonline.org](http://www.bbbonline.org/) or [https://www.usa.gov/privacy](https://www.usa.gov/privacy).

### More About Honeyfund

### Tips & Resources

### Follow Us

### Safe and Secure

*   [ ](https://www.stripe.com/)The Stripe name and logos are trademarks or service marks of Stripe, Inc. or its affiliates in the U.S. and other countries. Other names may be trademarks of their respective owners.
* 

© 2005-2024 [Honeyfund.com, Inc](https://www.honeyfund.com/). All rights reserved.

Use of Honeyfund constitutes acceptance of our [Terms of Use](https://www.honeyfund.com/Terms) & [Privacy Policy](https://www.honeyfund.com/Privacy).
